# **Vitaliy Kozakevich**



Khmelnytskyi

#### **Profile**

I am an open-minded person, who is highly motivated and passionate about web development. During my studies at university, I got experience in the basics of computer sciences and decided to further develop my skills in these sectors. Active team member with leadership skills.

Skills

CSS	• • • • •
Redux	• • • • •
HTML5	• • • • •
React	• • • • •
Git	• • • • •
JavaScript	• • • • •
Jira	• • • • •
Tailwind CSS	• • • • •
Languages	
<b>Ukrainian</b> Native	
<b>English</b> Upper-Intermediate	
Russian C2	

## **Professional Experience**

**Frontend Developer,** Dev Smile Sep 2023 – present Khmelnytskyi, Ukraine The platform allows a user to create/edit web sites, online shops, works with templates, etc. Also, this project is a minimally viable product that was developed on the basis of a ready-made solution for bots.

**Frontend Developer,** *Dev Smile* Feb 2023 – Sep 2023 Khmelnytskyi, Ukraine A platform enables clients to easily develop/publish chatbots to web apps, and chat services such as Telegram, Viber, Facebook Messenger, and other popular channels. The platform gives you tools and modules to easily build a chat bot with any complexity: question-answer; integration with third-party services, etc.

# **Education**

Master of CS, Khmelnytskyi National University

Sep 2023 – present Khmelnytskyi, Ukraine

#### Courses

**Front-end Development course** Sep 2023 - Nov 2023

Khmelnytskyi

### **Interests**

Hobbyhorsing